Let's give a big round of applause to Kamal Four's star
cut.
You have to make saffron rasgulla.
Let's donut.
Ajay ji is a very good cook.
No brother Ajay sir please come.
I have never made Rasgulla.
Just soaked it and ate it.
Brother, would you like some tea or coffee?   Then do it.
Sir, how much flour should I knead?  The flour paste is sticking.
Actually, Ajay doesn't even need to add lemon.  She
bursts just by looking at them.
Watch on the hand, watch around the neck.  What are you telling
people?
After Teja's arrival, I am a guest for two hours.   Have you
put this?  Deco Pay came.  Decor
came on deck, right?
This was made by Ajay Sir.
Everyone is distributing bills in my name, friend.
Why does it seem as if the child has come back from the bathroom in the morning?
How is your jaw lines for sharp?
I also eat barley bread.
Ajay Sir, have you ever eaten Nooni Ghee?
What?
Nooni ghee.
Where does this come from?
From Haryana.
They are saying that they will have to take permission from you.
For marriage.
Hey, he is adding fuel to our fire.
Actually, we both put one too.  You have already
seen it.  I love you my friend, I
love you with my eyes.
As I said, here food will be cooked,
humour will also be cooked and the one whose food is the worst,
we will bring him down from the sky to the ground.
Oh brother,
what is this?   Come